Sinners is a thriller film directed by Charles T. Kanganis.
Love is in the air in a small Italian neighborhood of New York.
But, is it safe to cheat on your wife, with your cousin, whose
brother owns a shotgun and whose hobby is blowing up cars?
Father Al, played by Joe Palese.
Geno, played by Robert Gallo.
Jerry, played by Joey Travolta.
Max, played by Robert Tiffe.
Francis, played by Wendy MacDonald.
Mona / Prostitute, played by Sabrina Ferrand.
Delroy George Lindo (born 18 November 1952) is an American actor.
Starting his career in the 1975 stage production Of Mice and Men, he later earned a Tony Award nomination
for Best Featured Actor for his work in the 1988 production of Joe Turner's Come and Gone.
He received wider recognition with roles in several Spike Lee films, playing West Indian Archie in Malcolm X (1992), Woody Carmichael in Crooklyn (1994), Rodney Little in Clockers (1995), and Paul, a
Vietnam War veteran in Da 5 Bloods (2020), the latter of which earned him the New York Film Critics Circle Award for Best Actor and the National Society of Film Critics Award for Best Actor.
For his role as Delta Slim in Ryan Coogler's Sinners (2025), he was
nominated for the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.
Lindo is also known for playing Bo Catlett in Get Shorty (1995), Arthur Rose in The Cider House Rules (1999), Detective Castlebeck in Gone in 60
Seconds (2000), Isaak O'Day in Romeo Must Die (2000) Joe Black in This Christmas (2007), and Bass Reeves in The Harder They Fall (2021).
He also voiced the character Beta in the Pixar animated film Up (2009).
On television, he portrayed Matthew Henson in the 1998 television film Glory & Honor,
and Supreme Court Judge Clarence Thomas in Strange Justice (1999).
Lindo later starred as Alderman Ronin Gibbons in the series The Chicago Code (2011), as Winter in the
fantasy drama series Believe (2014), and as Adrian Boseman in The Good Fight (2017–2021).
The tone is intense.